

Travis WRIGHT

www.coderfoundry.com/traviswright

FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5
CSS3
JavaScript/ES6
JQuery
Bootstrap
.NET
C#
MVC
ASP.NET
SQL & Bash
LINQ
Xamarin

WebAPI

CODER

1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer

Kernersville, NC · April 2019–June 2019

- Created three primary projects, including:
 - 1. A portfolio site using C#, MVC, HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JS & jQuery.
 - 2. A Financial Portal implemented in three phases. Phase 1: an MVC Web Application, Phase 2: a Web Service that utilizes Swagger and Swashbuckle for integrated testing, Phase 3: A cross platform Xamarin Mobile Application.
 - 3. Fully designed and developed a multi-functional issue tracker web application, implementing enhanced roles & security, which also used a Code First Relational database designed and modeled in SQL Server. Technologies used include: .Net Framework v. 4.6.1, MVC5, C#, LINQ, SQL, Entity Framework, jQuery DataTables.

American AV, Operations Manager

Raleigh, NC · 2018–2019

- Assisted the Regional Manager in day to day operations and logistics for a live events audiovisual company.
- Solely responsible for operational duties including warehouse supervision, labor scheduling, freelancer coordination and hiring, equipment scheduling, and small sales.
- Day to day scheduling of all full-time technicians, drivers, freelancers, and crew companies for warehouse, local hotel properties, and live events.
- Day to day scheduling of all inventory in the NC warehouse.
- Coordinated with the Project Managers to ensure all equipment needed was scheduled for each event.

ST Audio, Owner

Thomasville, NC · 2013–2018

- Sold, supported, installed, and repaired computer, network, sound, video, projection automation, website, and any other technology needs.
- Contracted by local small business's to be IT support for all their technology needs.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

PMG Research Inc., Media Associate/Support Coordinator

Winston-Salem, NC · 2008–2013

- Supported 250 end users.
- Supported computer systems including 15 physical servers/4 VMWare Servers, technology hardware, administrate phone systems and company cell phones, printers, copiers, managing Active Directory, and network connectivity for 11 offices.
- Job duties were a mix of graphic design, TV Productions, and Audio Productions.
- Created templates and ads for publications such as flyers, brochures and billboards.
- Created all TV and Radio Commercials in-house using Adobe software and professional grade audio and video equipment.
- Created education videos to help people learn and know who we are.
- Responsible for Tier 2 HelpDesk ticket issues.
- Trained new staff on computer systems, and hardware.
- Managed technology resources for new offices and renovation of offices.
- Supported all issue's that deal with technology.

EDUCATION

Capella University, Information Technology Studies

Minneapolis, MN · 2013

